<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="de.openms.knime.dynamicJSViewers.feature"
      label="OpenMS JavaScript Views"
      version="1.0.0.qualifier">

   <description>
This package was developed as part of the MODAL project and adds JavaScript
visualizations for mass-spectrometry data to KNIME.
It is intended to be used together with the KNIME OpenMS plugin.
OpenMS is an open-source software C++ library for LC/MS data management and 
analyses. It offers an infrastructure for the development of mass 
spectrometry related software and powerful 2D and 3D visualization.

OpenMS is free software available under the three clause BSD license and runs 
under Windows, MacOSX and Linux.
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright Zuse Institute Berlin and Freie Universitaet Berlin 2021.
   </copyright>

   <license>
      BSD 3-Clause License

--------------------------------------------------------------------------
                  OpenMS KNIME JS Views
--------------------------------------------------------------------------
Copyright Zuse Institute Berlin and Freie Universitaet Berlin 2021.

This software is released under a three-clause BSD license:
 * Redistributions of source code must retain the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer.
 * Redistributions in binary form must reproduce the above copyright
   notice, this list of conditions and the following disclaimer in the
   documentation and/or other materials provided with the distribution.
 * Neither the name of any author or any participating institution
   may be used to endorse or promote products derived from this software
   without specific prior written permission.
For a full list of authors, refer to the file AUTHORS.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------
THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED BY THE COPYRIGHT HOLDERS AND CONTRIBUTORS &quot;AS IS&quot;
AND ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTIES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE
IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE
ARE DISCLAIMED. IN NO EVENT SHALL ANY OF THE AUTHORS OR THE CONTRIBUTING
INSTITUTIONS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL,
EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,
PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE GOODS OR SERVICES; LOSS OF USE, DATA, OR PROFITS;
OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION) HOWEVER CAUSED AND ON ANY THEORY OF LIABILITY,
WHETHER IN CONTRACT, STRICT LIABILITY, OR TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE OR
OTHERWISE) ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE USE OF THIS SOFTWARE, EVEN IF
ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="de.openms.knime.dynamicJSViewers"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
